The Princeton Review and Tutor.com Privacy Policy
=================================================

_Effective Date: June 4, 2024_

Tutor.com, Inc. and TPR Education, LLC d/b/a The Princeton Review (collectively, “we,” “us,” or “our”) take your privacy seriously and understand the importance of protecting your personal information. Therefore, this Privacy Policy provides information about our privacy practices. “Personal information” means, unless otherwise defined by applicable law, any information about, that identifies, that relates to, that is linked to or associated with, or that is reasonably linkable to or reasonably capable of being associated with an identified or identifiable individual. For clarity, this Privacy Policy does not apply to our employees, job applicants, and independent contractors.

By visiting this site and other websites and mobile applications which link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “Sites”) or using the products or services offered through this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms of Use for this Site.

**Availability of Anonymous Access**

Depending on the organization through which you access our online, on-demand tutoring programs, you can access the program through a guest account, an anonymous account, or a personalized account.

If you access the program through a guest account, we do not collect personal information such as your name or email address from you to create an account. Certain features of the program will not be available to you, such as voice or videos sessions, essay drop off review, or storage of past sessions.

If you access the program through an anonymous account, then the email address you used to create an individual account is only stored in our system as an un-recognizable “hash” of letters and numbers, using an irreversible encryption algorithm. Therefore, you will not receive email communication of any kind from us, and certain features of the program will not be available to you, such as voice or videos sessions and essay drop off review.

The benefit to a personalized account is to make available certain features of the service like:

* Making your sessions personal;
* Access to voice and, when generally available, video sessions, and essay drop off review;
* Storing all of your past sessions, so you can review them anytime; and
* Access to our mobile application.

**Children under the Age of 13**

Depending on the organization through which you access our program, you use our program through a guest account (as described above), an anonymous account (as described above), or a personalized account with the permission of your parent or legal guardian (obtained by your school or provided by your school on behalf of your parent or legal guardian if you are using our program through your school or obtained by us) for us to collect, use, or disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Note to parents of children under the age of 13: You are welcome to contact us at (800) 411-1970 to review any personal information we have collected about your child. You may request that we delete this information or specify that we collect no more of your child's information. We will need to verify the identity of anyone requesting information about a child under the age of 13 to ensure that the person is in fact the child' parent or legal guardian.

**Information We Collect**

We collect information through the sources described below.

Information You Provide to Us. Except as described in the “Availability of Anonymous Access” section above, we may collect personal information and non-personal information from you (such as your name, email address, library card number, essays, and military or veteran status) when you:

* register or create an account on our Site;
* call us;
* provide or send us messages, documents, and other files and content in the course of your use of our products or services;
* enter sweepstakes or other promotions;
* respond to surveys or questionnaires or submit testimonials;
* provide us information on our Site or submit online forms so that we can answer questions you have; or
* when you provide us information by other means.

Information from Third Parties.

We may collect personal and non-personal information about you (such as your name, email address, username, student ID number, school name, grade level, and courses you are taking) from third parties with whom we have a business relationship (such as our organizational customers and resellers).

Information Collected Automatically.

We collect information (such as your IP address, machine ID, your browser type, cookies, the referring website address, and operating system) from your browser when you visit our Site.

We, our service providers and other vendors, and our affiliates and third parties which may display advertisement on our Site may use tracking technologies such as cookies to collect information about your online interactions with our Site and our emails.

We collect information when you use our products and services (such as when we record online sessions and produce transcripts of online tutoring sessions).

We automatically record calls to our call center.

**How We Use Information**

We may use your personal information to:

* provide you with and personalize our products and services;
* create and manage your account and provide you customer service;
* maintain our internal records, comply with legal requirements, and otherwise manage our business;
* send you newsletters and otherwise correspond with you about our products, services, and events that we think may interest you;
* ask for your reviews and testimonials and send you surveys and questionnaires;
* administer sweepstakes and other promotions;
* develop and display content tailored to your interests on our Site;
* perform research and analysis about your use of our products and services and our Site;
* detect, prevent, or investigate illegal activity or misuse of our products or services and enforce our legal rights; and
* perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

We may use non-personal information for any lawful purpose.

**Third Parties to whom We Disclose Information**

We may disclose your information to third parties as described below. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

Organizations and Persons who Arrange for Your Participation in Our Programs

We work with schools, school districts, colleges and universities, local, state, and federal government agencies, businesses, and other organizations to provide programs such as tutoring, test preparation, and college admissions counseling. Your organization may arrange for your participation in these programs and negotiate a special price or trial offer, or purchase (or subsidize) products or services on your behalf. We may disclose your personal and non-personal information that we collect through your participation in these programs (such as test scores, transcripts or recordings of online tutoring and online class sessions, comments you leave in post-session surveys, and details regarding your usage of our programs) to the organization arranging for your access to these programs or to your parents or guardians. In addition, your school may require us to disclose such information to others legally entitled to access your academic records, such as your state department of education.

Service Providers and Other Vendors

We may disclose your personal information to our service providers and other vendors, such as those who provide tools for communicating and exchanging information with customers, help us manage our relationships with customers, provide tools for online forms and surveys, analyze online activity, provide online hosting and storage services, and otherwise help deliver our products and services and operate our business.

Legally Compelled Disclosures and Safety

We may disclose personal information when compelled to do so by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law, such as to respond to court orders and subpoenas. We may also disclose personal information to protect the safety of others and when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interfering with our rights or property or the rights or property of others.

Business Transfer

If we or all or a portion of our business is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, personal information may be included in the transferred assets.

Authorized Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information to third parties when you authorize the disclosure.

Non-Personal Information

We may disclose non-personal Information to any third party for any lawful purpose.

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Users of Your Organization's Tutoring Services (If You are a Tutor for Your Organization)**

Some of our organizational customers may choose to provide tutoring services to their users through our platform using their own tutors. If you are a tutor for such an organizational customer, then we may disclose your personal information to your organizational customer's users.

**Your Access to Information**

If you have an account with us, you may review and correct the information that is accessible to you under the settings for your account on our Site or by calling 800-411-1970.

**Using Caution when Sharing Information with Others**

When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Site, such as a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, or wiki, the information that you submit will be made available to the general public. Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information to such areas of our Site, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information or any other information that would enable other users to locate you or contact you.

**Other Sites**

When you are on our Site, you may be able to visit or link to other sites not operated by us. We do not control such sites and are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites, and we encourage you to read the posted privacy policies of such sites.

**Users in U.S. States with Privacy Laws**

We are a processor or service provider to the organization through which you access our services. Please contact the organization to exercise your rights under state privacy laws.

**Users Outside of the United States**

By providing personal information to this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, in accordance with applicable law. We operate in and market to individuals primarily in the United States and Canada, and we do not operate in or market to individuals in the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom. The processing by us of personal information of individuals outside of the United States or Canada is generally incidental. We do, however, recognize the privacy-related rights of individuals in countries which provide such rights, and therefore, request that any such individuals who have questions about or requests related to the personal information we collect to contact us at [privacy@review.com](mailto:privacy@review.com).

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Site from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you may contact us by email or mail at the following address:

The Princeton Review and Tutor.com  
110 E. 42nd Street, 7th Floor   
New York, NY 10017  
Attention: Legal Department  

[Terms of Use](https://lhh.tutor.com/policies/terms-of-use.htm) | Privacy Policy | [Frequently Asked Questions](https://lhh.tutor.com/policies/faq.aspx)
